<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Yes Mobile</string>
    <string name="FCM_PREF">com.theyestech.yes_mobile.fcm_pref</string>
    <string name="FCM_TOKEN">com.theyestech.yes_mobile.fcm_token</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="mission">theyestech.com is a company built on the foundation of revolutionizing digital technology services in different platforms. We are optimistic that this company will help people maximize their capabilities and improve their quality of life and way of learning upon using our services. The companys thrust is mainly on bridging the gap created by technology by creating techno friendly and easy to use applications, programs, and websites. With a viable and dedicated team and a leader that will take them to new heights theyestech.com is bound to serve the City, Region, and Country with tremendous commitment and vigor. Our values are anchored on Integrity, Accountability, and Responsibility in serving our customers, stakeholders, and investors. Join us Revolutionize Digital Technology!</string>
    <string name="vision">Yestech is the brainchild of its founder Ms.Reyes. As an Educator, she has devoted over 20 years of her life serving students through development of quality education. Yestech was created in order to assist Educators in bridging the learning gap that technology has created. With the availability of the service, students will definitely find interest in this interactive learning platform and will capture their attention. This tool was created in order to reach learners even in the most far flung area (hinterlands). With yestech.com, students are given the opportunity to create and become innovative, since this application is available even for offline work. Videos and interactive participation is encouraged making learning a partnership between teacher and students. In todays digital age, leaders of education have to embrace change and make sure they are available in aiding their students with new technology and learning. With "theyestech" engaging students to take a proactive approach towards learning has never been easier. Try our service for free and your students will feel the empowerment of making learning a lifelong engagement and experience. Students progress are monitored and videos are available for student engagement, Assessment and participation in various lessons through video uploads will make learning fruitful and truly a fun experience. Creativity among educators and students in uploading videos will be challenged as well. Embark our fun digital learning adventure with the yestech.com</string>
</resources>
