<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Yes Mobile</string>
    <string name="FCM_PREF">com.theyestech.yes_mobile.fcm_pref</string>
    <string name="FCM_TOKEN">com.theyestech.yes_mobile.fcm_token</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="mission">theyestech.com is a company built on the foundation of revolutionizing digital technology services in different platforms. We are optimistic that this company will help people maximize their capabilities and improve their quality of life and way of learning upon using our services. The companys thrust is mainly on bridging the gap created by technology by creating techno friendly and easy to use applications, programs, and websites. With a viable and dedicated team and a leader that will take them to new heights theyestech.com is bound to serve the City, Region, and Country with tremendous commitment and vigor. Our values are anchored on Integrity, Accountability, and Responsibility in serving our customers, stakeholders, and investors. Join us Revolutionize Digital Technology!</string>
    <string name="vision">Yestech is the brainchild of its founder Ms.Reyes. As an Educator, she has devoted over 20 years of her life serving students through development of quality education. Yestech was created in order to assist Educators in bridging the learning gap that technology has created. With the availability of the service, students will definitely find interest in this interactive learning platform and will capture their attention. This tool was created in order to reach learners even in the most far flung area (hinterlands). With yestech.com, students are given the opportunity to create and become innovative, since this application is available even for offline work. Videos and interactive participation is encouraged making learning a partnership between teacher and students. In todays digital age, leaders of education have to embrace change and make sure they are available in aiding their students with new technology and learning. With "theyestech" engaging students to take a proactive approach towards learning has never been easier. Try our service for free and your students will feel the empowerment of making learning a lifelong engagement and experience. Students progress are monitored and videos are available for student engagement, Assessment and participation in various lessons through video uploads will make learning fruitful and truly a fun experience. Creativity among educators and students in uploading videos will be challenged as well. Embark our fun digital learning adventure with the yestech.com</string>

    <string name="iesa_award">Our Founder was awarded as the Most Outstanding Department Head and Coordinator in the Region, out of 8000 entries only 150 were chosen from 50 countries in the International Education Summit in Bangkok, Thailand last February 2020. Congratulations for representing the Philippines!</string>
    <string name="radio_interview">Our start up founder was interviewed by Radyo Bombo for her Innovation and for introducing a revolutionary platform that will benefit the students of the 21st century.</string>
    <string name="techtonic_festival">theyestech.com was sponsored by CDO Bites to exhibit at the Techtonic Festival. Various schools and different start-ups were showcased. There was a pitching competition as well . The Founder was able to meet CEO’s and people like her , driven and inspired! Through the Festival the founder met with interested schools and Principals. It was indeed a good exposure for our e-learning platform.</string>
    <string name="bench_marking_amihan">Our founder had the opportunity to meet the founder of Amihan , Mr. Winston Damarillo he is a venture capitalist and is very successful with this work. He is looking for the first Unicorn in the Philippines. Every start-up wants to be this , he talked about , KUMU and how it is being funded by the Gokongwei group for 500 million pesos. It is indeed exciting . Secretary Guevarra joined our meeting and ate with our founder . After the session, Secretary Guevarra gave a message telling the founders not to quit or sell –out early. Also , yestech had the priviledge to share their pitchdeck to Secretary Guevarra for her to present at Silicon Valley.</string>
    <string name="bench_marking_qbo">Our founder had the chance to visit Manila together with the other CDO BITES incubates. The benchmarking session started at QBO . QBO helps start-ups succeed , one of their mentors Natasha Bautista used to work for Grab and was responsible for making it where it is now!</string>
    <string name="yestech_valencia">Through the kindness of D.O.S.T and CDO B.I.T.E.S , theyestech.com was able to join the exhibit held at Robinson’s place Valencia . Interested students and educators listened to our Founder share her experience and the good news about our learning platform. The innovation lounge was the venue for the presentation , in which students and other interested people came to listen. It was indeed a successful exhibit .</string>
    <string name="puntod_national_highschool">Teachers from Puntod National High School were presented with our yestech.com platform . The teachers were excited to participate and do the hands on work in their computer lab. This is indeed exciting for them as they have been using another platform which they think is comparable with our work . In fact yestech.com is more user-friendly they say. Thank you Puntod National HighSchool!</string>
    <string name="yestech_ginoog">Education knows no boundaries ! In order to help schools become connected with technology . Our founder together with her team of 2 PhD students and 1 developer visited Gingoog City . The principal of Odiongan Elementary School Mr. Nicomar Butalid together with 40 instructors were given a Workshop in effectively using the learning platform provided by theyestech.com. It was a fun and wonderful experience for the Teachers as they embrace technology and change.</string>
    <string name="philippine_start">The event was held at the Crowne Plaza , startups from different parts of the Philippines were showcased . This time , theyestech.com founder attended talks given by successful founders. Angeline Tahm, the founder of Angkas was there to talk about her struggles and her inpiration for starting the service.</string>


    <string name="account_settings">In order to manage content and infomation about your profile, your activities, progress, and prefered contents, contacts you may update this feature. It basically will store information you voluntarily share in a generalized form.</string>
    <string name="personal_info">This refers to the name you share, phone number, correspondence or email addresses as well as contact number.</string>
    <string name="language">This page encourage educator and student to use English Language however it is not limited to that. Language and translation preference is also accomodated provided that violations of our policies are not compromised.</string>
    <string name="payments">Manage your settings in terms of payments of courses learning materials as well as our online bookstore.</string>
    <string name="security">In order to have a secure and safe experience, a password must be encoded at all times. Like most app and websites. Please make sure you do not share it with others.</string>
    <string name="security_login">We suggest that you change your password every year or six months to ptotect your account from getting hacked.</string>
    <string name="app_websites">Make sure you are able to manage the information you share with apps and website youve login to with Yestech.com.</string>
    <string name="limitation">This learning platform is a tool for educators to help students with their learning. The Yestech.com does not guarantee leaps and bounds in terms of progress as it is the students initiative to take advantage of this offering.</string>
    <string name="nudity">The Yestech.com will implement suspension expulsion and will block Educators and Students that post, share, create materials, videos, and even chat that may be offensive, abusive or violate policies. This platform was created to accomodate learning and will exercise to the fullest what is lawful and just. We may forward pertinent information to proper channels in order to enforce the law.</string>
    <string name="report">An educator or a student can report offensive materials and violations to the system admin. Your report will be processed and handled after a through, assessment, evaluation and investigation.</string>




</resources>
